<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  SPDX-FileCopyrightText: none
-->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kdebugsettingsquick</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1-or-later</project_license>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <name>KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">K Hata Ayıklama Ayarları</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDebugSettings</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KDebug 設定</name>
  <summary>Set which debug messages are shown</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Estableix quins missatges de depuració es mostraran</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Establix quins missatges de depuració es mostraran</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Definir los mensajes de depuración que se deben mostrar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Définir quels messages de débogage sont affichés</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">הגדרת אילו הודעות ניפוי שגיאות תוצגנה</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Stelt in welke debugberichten getoond worden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Define quais mensagens de depuração são exibidas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Nastavi, katera sporočila o napakah so prikazana</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Hangi hata ayıklama ayarlarının görüntüleneceğini ayarlayın</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Визначення того, які з діагностичних повідомлень буде показано</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">設定要顯示哪些除錯訊息</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KDebugSettings edits which QLoggingCategory are displayed. QLoggingCategory prints messages on the console for applications and you can define which applications display messages for information, warning or critical errors to help debugging Qt applications.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDebugSettings edita quina «QLoggingCategory» es mostrarà. La «QLoggingCategory» imprimeix missatges a la consola de les aplicacions, de manera que podreu definir quines aplicacions mostraran missatges informatius, avisos o errors crítics per a ajudar a depurar les aplicacions Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDebugSettings edita quina «QLoggingCategory» es mostrarà. La «QLoggingCategory» imprimix missatges en la consola de les aplicacions, de manera que podreu definir quines aplicacions mostraran missatges informatius, avisos o errors crítics per ajudar a depurar les aplicacions Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Las preferencias de KDebug escogen la QLoggingCategory que se muestra. QLoggingCategory muestra mensajes de las aplicaciones en la consola. Aquí puede definir los mensajes que muestran las aplicaciones para informaciones, advertencias o errores críticos, para ayudarle a depurar aplicaciones de Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KDebugSettings modifie quels éléments « QLoggingCategory » sont à afficher. QLoggingCategory imprime des messages sur la console pour les applications. Vous pouvez définir quelles applications affichent des messages d'informations, d'avertissements ou d'erreurs critiques pour faciliter le débogage des applications sous Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">KDebugSettings עורך אילו קטגוריות QLoggingCategory תוצגנה. QLoggingCategory מדפיסה הודעות במסוף ליישומים ואפשר להגדיר אילו יישומים יציגו הודעות לקבלת פרטים, אזהרה או שגיאות משמעותיות כדי לסייע בניפוי שגיאות ביישומי Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDebugSettings bewerkt welke QLoggingCategory worden getoond. QLoggingCategory toont meldingen op de console voor toepassingen en u kunt definiëren welke toepassingen berichten voor informatie tonen, waarschuwing of kritische fouten om Qt toepassingen te helpen bij debuggen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KDebugSettings permite definir quais QLoggingCategory são exibidas. As categorias de log exibem mensagens no console para as aplicações, e você pode determinar quais delas mostram mensagens informativas, de aviso ou de erro crítico, auxiliando assim na depuração de aplicações Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KDebugSettings ureja, katere kategorije QLoggingCategory so prikazane. QLoggingCategory izpisuje sporočila v konzoli za aplikacije in določite lahko, katere aplikacije prikazujejo sporočila z informacijami, opozorili ali kritičnimi napakami, kar pomaga pri odpravljanju napak v aplikacijah Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">K Hata Ayıklama Ayarları, hangi QLoggingCategory’lerin görüntüleneceğini düzenler. QLoggingCategory, uygulamalar için konsola iletiler yazdırır ve Qt uygulamalarında hata ayıklamaya yardımcı olmak için hangi uygulamaların bilgi, uyarı veya kritik hatalar için ileti göstereceğini tanımlayabilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою програми «Параметри KDebug» можна визначити, які дані з QLoggingCategory буде показано. QLoggingCategory виводить повідомлення до консолі для програм, а ви можете визначити, для яких програм слід показувати повідомлення з відомостями, попередженнями або критичними помилками. Ці повідомлення допоможуть вам діагностувати причини проблем із програмами на основі Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KDebugSettings 編輯哪些 QLoggingCategory 紀錄分類要被顯示。QLoggingCategory 為應用程式在主控台顯示訊息，而您可以定義應用程式是否顯示資訊、警告或嚴重錯誤，來幫助除錯 Qt 應用程式。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kdebugsettings</url>
  <url type="help">https://doc.qt.io/qt-6/qloggingcategory.html</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kdebugsettings&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/kdebugsettings/</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://invent.kde.org/utilities/kdebugsettings</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kdebugsettingsquick.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>The main window of KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">La finestra principal del KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">La finestra principal de KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La ventana principal de KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La fenêtre principale de KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">החלון הראשי של KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Het hoofdvenster van KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">A janela principal do KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavno okno KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">K Hata Ayıklama Ayarları ana penceresi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно KDebugSettings.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">KDebugSettings 的主視窗。</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdebugsettings/kdebugsettings.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kdebugsettingsquick</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
  </releases>
</component>
